dogproblems.com 2013-11-22

# Privacy Policy | Adam's Dog Training & Dog Behavior

We are strongly committed to safeguarding subscribers’ privacy on this web site.

We operate under the following strict privacy policy:

The only information we obtain about our subscribers is information we need to process credit card charges for subscription fees. The information collected is never revealed, sold, or made public for any reason.

Personally identifiable information provided by subscribers (name, email or home address, etc.) is never disclosed to any individual or business.

**Cookies**  
Each time a subscriber logs into this web site, we store a temporary ‘cookie’ in the browser files of that subscriber’s computer. This cookie is used during your online session to allow you free access to the Subscribers Area, without repeatedly requiring you to re-enter your user name and password. When you log off or leave the site, the cookies file is automatically removed.

**External Links**  
In order to provide visitors with greater value, some of our pages may provide links to various third party websites. In no case is subscriber information or ‘cookies’ provided to the third party sites. However, keep in mind that many sites do attempt to capture visitor information when you browse those sites. Once you leave our site, we are not able to alert you should another site attempt to gather information from your browser.

**Private Forums**  
We provide our subscribers with a multi-tiered Discussion Forum that makes sharing information with other subscribers easy. To protect your privacy when posting or replying to messages in the message board, your personal information and email is not revealed. However, remember that any information you disclose in the message board areas can be read by all other subscribers, so exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**  
We use a variety of security measures including encryption and authentication from Thawte to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information under our control.

**Choice/Opt-In**  
Our site gives users the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. You can be assured that we never reveal, sell, or make available your email address to anyone for any purpose. This site also gives users options for removing their information from our database in order to stop receiving our communications.

**Other**

•Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet.  
•Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website.  
•Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. (Alternatively you can point users to opt out of a third party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.)

If you’re using Remarketing Dynamic Ads, your privacy policy should also inform users that this feature uses the Teracent cookie and that users may opt out of the Teracent cookie by visiting the Teracent opt-out page.

If you’re using DoubleClick’s remarketing pixels, your privacy policy may instead tell users to opt out of DoubleClick’s use of cookies by visiting the DoubleClick opt-out page or the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

Because advertiser sites and laws across countries/territories vary, we’re unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) for guidance on drafting a privacy policy.

If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, feel free to contact us.
